本字幕由 YYeTs人人影视 翻译制作
更多美剧更新 请登陆 www.YYeTs.net
■
《反恐24小时》前情提要
Previously on 24
这究竟是怎么一回事
What the hell is this?!
所有监视东部区域的屏幕都被锁定了
All our screens for the eastern quadrant are locked.
我已经把你的空管权弄到手了
I took out your control units.
我想让你看看我们的能力
I want you to see what we can do.
让他们准备改变航线
Get ready to make the course change
GSA117  这里是东北三号
Gsa 117, this is northeast three control.
请讲  航管局
Go ahead, air traffic control.
我们给你分配了一条新的降落跑道
We have a new runway assignment for you.
该死  这架飞机从右四跑道降落
Sid, there's another plane landing on four-right.
它正好穿过左31跑道
It crosses three-one-left.
GSA 117  请拉升
Gsa 117, pull up.
又四跑道  马上拉升
Four-right, pull up.
刚才不过是一个警告
That was just a warning shot.
下一次
Whatever we do next
我们会来真格的
It'll be the real thing.
把仪器准备好
Get the module ready.
按要求设计的
As promised.
朱玛上校会对此很满意的
General juma will be pleased.
现在是时候了
Perhaps now would be a good time
和泰勒总统交涉
to make your demands known to president taylor.
准备一下
Make the preparations.
现在他们将付出巨大的代价
Your government is about to pay a very steep price for...
涉足我们的私事
...interfering in our affairs.
他们认为我儿子是自杀
They assumed my son killed himself
因此对他的案子草草了之
They didn't look deeply enough into anything.
先生  当局已经对你儿子女友进行询问了
The authorities have already questioned your son's girlfriend, sir.
告诉我事实  否则你别想走
You're not going anywhere till I get the truth.
你知道杀害我儿子的凶手
You know who murdered my son.
他是自杀的
He killed himself
我会找出事情真相的
I'm gonna find what you are hiding.
到那时谁也救不了你
When I do, God helf you.
没错  他不是我们的人
You're right. he's not one of ours.
跟踪他  看看能否带我们找到托尼·阿尔梅达
We'll follow him, see if he leads us back to almeida-- dornan.
不  这样做不对
No, that's not the right move.
这事不能让其它人知道
You can't bring anyone else into this,
你究竟在干什么
What the hell's going on?
我们在查别的线索
We're following up on a lead.
一有发现  我第一时间向你汇报
And I will fill you in if and when we find something.
我不喜欢这样
I do not like this.
我厌倦了欺骗我的上司
I just flat out lied to my boss.
我告诉你帮你找到托尼·阿尔梅达
I told you I'd help you find Tony Almeida.
但你要让我按我的方法来做
But you're going to have to let me do it my way.
托尼  不许动
Tony, stop.
仪器不见了
Device is gone.
定位器记录已经被删除了
The locator files have been deleted.
在哪里
Where is it?!
你到底是怎么了
What the hell happened to you?
以下事件发生于上午十点至十一点
阿尔梅达现在在哪里
Where is almeida now?
他正在押送往FBI总部的途中
He is in transit to FBI headquarters
他会在那里接受审讯
He'll be formally interrogated there.
我搞不懂  阿尔梅达主导了这次事件
I don't understand. Almeida was orchestrating this attack.
如果他没有CIP装置  那它在谁的手里
If he doesn't have the CIP device, who does?
FBI得知阿尔梅达把芯片交给了别人
The FBI has learned that Almeida haned off the device
我们目前还不知道他是谁
to someone else,we don't know who.
我可以回答这个问题  总统阁下
I may have answer to that question, madam president.
请说
I'm listening.
阿尔梅达在替朱玛政府干活
He's working with the Juma regime.
大约5分钟之前
Approximately 5 minutes ago,
我们在内部网络上收到了这份声讯
an audio message was routed to the State Department's subnet.
杜巴库上校搞的鬼
It's from Colonel Dubaku
他是朱玛的忠实部下
He's Juma's right-hand man.
桑加拉出名的屠夫
He's known as the butcher in Sangala.
死在他手下了有30万人
Over three hundred thousand people were murdered.
我知道这个家伙
I know who he is.
这条声讯的内容是什么
What did the message say?
你自己听吧
You should hear it yourself.
泰勒总统
President Taylor
我是杜巴库
This is Colonel Ike Dubaku.
我想你们一定明白
As you have no doubt confirmed,
肯尼迪机场发生的不是意外事件
the near-collison at JFK international was no accident
芯片在我们的手中
We have the CIP device.
我们随时可以杀死成千上万美国人
We have the capability to kill tens of thousansds of Americans.
我们也正准备这么做
And we are prepared to do so.
我要求你方立刻并彻底得
We demand the complete and immediate withdrawal
撤走海军打击力量
of the US naval strike force
在明早此时之前撤出23子午线
to a position west of 23rd meridian by this time tommorrow.
为了保证撤离行动按时进行
In order to meet this timeline
我们要求使用你们的卫星
We require a satellite confirmation within three hours.
来证明航母的完全撤离
that the Carrier Air Wing is in full retreat.
不要让你士兵做无谓的牺牲了
Don't sacrifice your fellow countryman.
总统阁下
Madam president
请允许桑加拉人民决定自己的命运吧
Allow the people of Sangala to determine their own destiny.
撤离你的军队
Stand your forces down.
声音89%吻合
Voice prints an 89% match.
是杜巴库  毫无疑问
It's Dubaku. There's little doubt.
您先前的猜测是正确的  总统阁下
Looks like your suspicion were correct, madam president.
这两件事情确实有关联
This is about Africa.
我的天  杜巴库早就为这场战争在做准备了
My god. Dubaku should have been tried for war crimes years ago.
现在他给我们最后通牒
Now he's giving us ultimatums.
我们绝不能让他以美国为要挟
We can not let this monster hold our country hostage.
我们的飞机情况如何
Where do we stand on the planes?
还有2500多架飞机未降落
They're still 2500 planes in the air
我们必须尽快改进我们的系统
We have got to shore up the firewall
这样CIP芯片就没有威胁了
so that the CIP device will be rendered useless.
我认为我们可以在6天内重设系统
We now think we can re-engineer the code in six days.
6天  我们连6小时都没有
Six days? We don't have the luxury of six hours!
对不起  总统阁下  这么短的时间
I'm sorry, madam president. But their is no way
我们无法重设系统
we can rebuild the firewall in that timeframe.
你去制定一个应对攻击的保密计划
I want you to instigate a series of restricted allerts.
通话仅限于机长
Keep it to the first responders only.
我希望我们能够准备好对付可能的攻击
I want people to be ready in case we are attacked again
但我不想造成恐慌
but we don't wanna start panic
好的  总统阁下
Yes, madam president
先生们  阿尔梅达现在是我们唯一的线索
And gentlemen, Almeida is our only lead.
告知FBI非洲的要求
Make sure the FBI is aware of the demands
让他们从非洲方面对阿尔梅达下手
and they need to work Almeida from the Africa side
告诉他们  我们的时间不多了
And they need to know we don't have a lot of time.
好的  总统阁下
Yes, ma'am.
快点
Come on
小心头
Put your head down
带他去审讯
Get him ready for questioning.
我需要你的解释
I want an explanation.
你们在没有后援和上级同意的情况下去了那艘船上
You went after that shooter without backup or authorization,
甚至拒绝告诉我这么做的原因
And then refused to tell me why.
我现在想知道这是为什么
Now i want to know
我们不知道谁会听得到我们的通话
We didn't know who might be listening
我们中间有内鬼
Someone in this office is helping Almeida
FBI被渗透了  有内奸
The FBI has been compromised, larry. there's a leak
你有什么根据  你干嘛
Based on what? Excuse me!
这是私人谈话
This is private
托尼在我们到达之前就得到了这个情报
Tony knew that we were going to Schector's office before we even got there
所以他才有时间布置狙击手
That's how he managed a sniper in position
内鬼一定是你的人
The tip had to come from your office,
不管他是谁  把他给找出来  让他滚蛋
whoever it was helped sheclter's assassinator got out of the building
他说得对  这就是为什么我们先前不能告诉你
He is right lerry, that's why we couldn't tell you
我们已经把狙击手包围了  每个出口都有我们的人
You've got a full perimeter, right?Covered every exit?
但他还是跑掉了
How else do you think he got out of there?
这事看起来很棘手  你知道内鬼是谁吗
All right, assuming this is true, you got any idea who it could be?
我们还不清楚   但他知道我们的行动
No, we didn't see him, but we knew that it went down
一定是局里的人
Could be anyone in the bureau
托尼  你必须管好你的人
You need tighten your circle around tony
你不能让他再把情报泄露出去了
You can't get any information that he gives you get back to the people
否则的话你永远找不到那块芯片
Other wise you will never get the CIP device
好吧 我会把安全等级调升到四
All right, I'll limit access the level 4 clearance above
查一下纪录  看看有没有可能找出内鬼
Have Janis run the security protocols see if she can track down the leak
我是moss
This's moss
白宫找你
Sir I have a white house call for you
-我去办公室接  -好的
-Yeah, I'll take it in my office -Yes
-再见
-Yea
是白宫
It's the white house
从现在开始  你不得再私自行动
From now on, keep me in the loop
特别是你要向我通报他的一切行动
And he doesn't do a damn thing without telling me
除了告诉他  我们别无选择
We had to tell him, We had no choice
他值得信任吗
You trust him?
当然  我最相信他了
No question, there is no one I trust more
他们会把托尼关在哪
Where they gonna hold tony?
我等下要把你的衣服提上去
Well, I'm gonna have to lift up your shirt
有什么不舒服的地方吗
Is that comfortable for you?
看起来你没事
I'll take that as a Yes
-怎么样了 -一切都准备好了
-Is he hooked up?-Yeah, we are ready to go
我来主持审讯  你有别的任务
Janis, I'll run this session, I want you to handle something else
什么任务
What else?
把泄密的人给找出来
Plugging a security leak
什么
What?
我们认为这里有人在帮助阿尔梅达
We think someone in this office has been helping Almeida
为此安全等级升到了四级
We've kicked this up to level four clearance.I want
你去看一下所有的通讯和情报纪录
you to vet all communication and information flow.
特别是和阿尔梅达有关的数据
Red-tag every data point that has to do with almeida.
好的  你知道那个人可能是谁吗
Okay, do we have any idea who it is?
不知道  我们希望你能够找出那个家伙来
No, we don't. I'm hoping that you can help us find out
好的
Okay
血压计有0.2的测量误差
There's a point-two deviation on the blood pressure monitor,
你得注意调整一下
you are gonna have to compensate for that
谢谢你
Thanks,Janis
杰克  我很遗憾他是你的朋友
Sorry about your friend Jack.
我知道你希望他从未做过此事
I know you were hoping he wasn't capable of doing something like this.
是的
Yea
这究竟是怎么一回事  为什么启用四级安全防范
Hey, what's going on, why are we in the level 4 lockdown?
别管它  做好你的工作就行
Don't worry about that, just do your job
我的安全权限无法获得资料
How am I supposed to do my job when
怎么进行工作
i can't get through half the server nodes in the building
你的任务是收集整理阿尔梅达留下的资料
You're sifting through the evidence gathered at almeida's arrest site
这不需要安全等级四的权限
That doesn't not require level 4 clearings
把你需要的东西准备好  继续工作吧
Get everything you need to do your work, PLEASE
好  我明白
Oui, je comprends
确定阿尔梅达在联调局那里
It's confirmed, the FBI has Almeida.
继续行动  这件事我们无能为力
We should move on, there's nothing we can do.
局内有我们的人  也许能把他救出来
We have assets inside the bureau, we use them, perhaps will get him out.
不行  太冒险
No, it's too risky.
那样做会破坏整个计划
We'd be jeopardizing the entire mission.
阿尔梅达没那么重要
Almeida is just not that important.
那下一项行动怎么办
What about the next operation?
托尼已经准备妥当  可以开始了
Tony is prepped, he's ready to go.
只能找别人了
We'll just gonna have to find someone else.
我知道你和托尼是朋友
I realized you and Tony are friends.
我也不想让他羊入虎口
I don't like throwing him to the wolves anymore than you do.
他也知道可能会有这个结果
But he knew what he was getting into.
我刚和朱玛通过电话
I just spoke with Juma
美军仍在我国附近驻扎
The American troops are still in position near our country.
请转告朱玛耐心些
Tell Juma to be patient,
泰勒总统刚收到你的要求
President Taylor just received your demands.
那或许我们该给他们更有力的回应
Then perhaps this time for a more forceful demonstration.
如果有那个必要  我们会做好准备
If it comes to that, we will be ready.
我们暂时要给白宫一些考虑的时间
For now, let's give the white house a little more time to respond.
暂时
For now.
沃克探员
Agent Walker.
阿尔梅达在为朱玛卖命
Almeida is working for the Juma reign.
什么意思
What are you talking about?
总统刚从埃克·杜巴库上校那里
The president just received a set of demands.
那里收到了一系列要求
They're from Colonel Ike Dubaku.
杜巴库
Dubaku?
看来他和阿尔梅达做了交易来制作CIP模块
Looks like he contracted Almeida to build the CIP module.
不  他会以此来要挟白宫
No, he's gonna blackmail the white house.
怎么要挟
How?
什么
Excuse me?
他要怎样要挟白宫
How is he gonna blackmail the white house?
坚持让我们从桑甘拉沿岸撤军
By insisting we stand down the invasion force of the coast Sangala.
假使总统不满足他的要求
If the president doesn't comply with his demands,
杜巴库就会开始杀害美国人
Dubaku is gonna start killing americans.
我可以给你拿到CIP装置
I can get you the CIP device.
让我和他谈谈
Just let me talk to him.
我认识他  知道他的想法
I know him, I might know how he thinks.
我们是旧相识  我会利用这点来对付他
We have a history, I can use it to agaist him.
他已经让我们走到这步  拉里
He's got us this far, Larry.
他说的有道理
It makes sense.
你们的时间所剩无几
You're running out of time.
你们没有更好的选择
You don't have a better option.
让我们单独在一起
Give us the room.
我看你死在我的怀里
I watched you die in my arms.
能告诉我你为何还活着吗
You wanna explain to me why you're still alive?
我猜也是
Didn't think so.
不如让我告诉你我知道些什么
Why don't I tell you what I know.
我知道你在为朱玛政权卖命
I know that you're working for Juma regime.
白宫刚收到他们的要求
The white house just got their demands.
你也一定知道我绝不会让他得逞
And you have to know that I will never let that happen.
你省省吧
Why don't you save yourself some time.
和皮肉之苦  告诉我CIP装置是什么
and some pain and tell me what CIP device is.
这我不能说  杰克
I can't tell you that, Jack.
托尼  你不仅将被控国内恐怖主义
Tony, you're not just facing charges of domestic terrorism,
还会因帮助及唆使种族灭绝
you were gonna face international charges
而受到国际指控
for aiding and abetting a genocide,
他们会判你死刑
They will give you the death penalty.
拜托  配合我一下
Come on, just work with me on this.
我可以帮你谈条件  甚至让你豁免
I can help you cut a deal, I can maybe even get you an immunity.
你在浪费唇舌
You're wasting your breath, Jack.
换做我  就会告诉总统撤军
If I were you, I would tell the president to withdraw those troops.
因为杜巴库心狠手辣
Because Dubaku is serious.
除非满足他的要求
He's ready to take thousands of american lives
否则几千名美国人就会丧生
unless his demands are met.
你到底为什么这么做
Why the hell are you doing this?
朱玛想要CIP模块  他想花钱买
Juma wanted the CIP module and he was brewing to pay for it.
我不信
I don't believe you.
不是吧  杰克
Oh, come on, Jack.
别表现的那么惊讶
Don't act so surprised.
我现在只为钱卖命
Money is the only reason I have left doing anything.
由政府来买单
The government took care of that.
不是政府害死了米歇尔
The government did not kill Michelle.
是查尔斯·洛根
Charles Logan did.
查尔斯·洛根不过是环境的产物
Charles Logan is the product of his enviroment.
是政府让他一步步走向泥潭
The government poisons everything in his path.
你比我更清楚这点  杰克
But you know that better than me, Jack.
他们把你害成了什么样
Look what they did to you.
可恶  托尼  咱们现在谈论的人不是我
Damn it, Tony, we're not talking about me.
不是吗
Oh, we're not?
你在问我为何这样做
You're asking me why I'm doing this.
我可以问你同样的问题
I could ask you the same question.
正是你为之卖命的这些人
Here you are, working for the same people
当初想把你送进监狱
who wanted to put you into the prison,
正是这些人夺走了你的至爱  让你一无所有
the same people who killed everything you love and left you with nothing,
你女儿不想与你扯上关系
your daughter wants nothing to do with you
闭嘴
Shut up.
还有奥德莉·瑞恩斯
Audrey Raines--
我让你闭嘴
I said shut up.
不  杰克  我不会闭嘴
No, Jack, no.
我得让你知道这些
You need to hear this.
你必须回归现实世界
You need to start living in the real world!
你为政府工作的每一刻
Because every second you help the government
都在令泰瑞的墓碑蒙羞  够了  起来
You're spitting on Teri's grave  Enough! get up!
起来
Get up!
他失去控制了
He's losing it
装置在哪?
where's the device?
装置在哪
Tell me where the device is!
我发誓我会杀了你
So help me god, I will kill you.
这次你不会再活过来了
And you will stay dead this time.
装置在哪
Where is the device?
最后一次机会
last chance.
装置在哪  在哪
Where is it? Where is it?
深邃天空
Deep sky.  Jack
你说什么
What did you just say?
杂种
Son of a bitch.
再给他点时间
Give him a few more seconds.
再给时间  他就死了
A few more seconds, he'll be dead.
深邃天空
Deep sky.
杰克  放开他
Jack. Let him go.
把他弄出去
Get him out of here.
把他弄出去  快
Get him out of here now.
快找医务人员  给他检查一下
I need a medic here to check him out. In here, please.
盯住他
Keep an eye on him.
深邃天空
Deep sky.
喂
Hello.
我是杰克·鲍尔
This is Jack Bauer.
说
Yes.
有人让我打给你
I was told to call you.
谁?
By whom?
托尼·阿尔梅达
Tony Almeida
他告诉我这个CTU旧的紧急电话
He gave me this old CTU emergency phone code.
深邃天空
Deep sky.
我是比尔  杰克
It's Bill, Jack.
比尔  究竟怎么回事
Bill, what the hell is going on?
托尼人呢
Where is Tony?
在FBI总部  他被逮捕了
FBI headquarters. He's been arrested.
逮捕了
Arrested?
他策划了今天的对美恐怖袭击
He orchastrated the terrorist attack on United States today.
我刚审讯过他
I was interrogating him.
你怎么参与进来的
How would you get involved in this?
FBI让我帮忙找到他
The FBI brought me in to help track him down.
我们需要谈谈  杰克
We need to talk, Jack.
我会用安全虚拟线路打给你
I'll call you back on a secure VPN line.
比尔  到底怎么回事
Bill, what the hell is going on?
给我10分钟设置虚拟网络
I need 10 minutes to set up the vpn...
10分钟太长了
I don't have 10 minutes.
就10分钟  杰克
10 minutes, Jack.
不敢相信
I can't believe this.
如果托尼被捕  那就完了
If Tony's been arrested, it's over
你打算告诉杰克真相吗
Are you gonna tell Jack everything?
想要让托尼恢复卧底
If we want to get Tony back under cover,
我们需要他
we will need his help.
我不认为目前杰克能帮到我们
I don't think Jack is in a very helpful frame of mind.
他是唯一的希望
He's our only hope.
你好  亨利
Hello, Henry
伊桑  桑加拉那里有消息
Ethan, I got your message about Sangala.
阿利森在哪
Where is Allison?
在她办公室
She's in her office.
亨利
Henry.
总统现在身处两难境地
The president is in an impossible situation right now.
她需要你的支持
She needs your support.
但你帮不了她
But you can't give it to her
除非你放弃对罗杰的疯狂猜想
if you keep going on this paranoid fantacies about Roger.
我知道萨曼莎·罗斯
I know about Samantha Roth.
我知道你今天去她办公室找她
I know you accosted her in her office.
我儿子被杀一事  她有事瞒着我
She's hiding something about my son's murder.
罗杰没有被杀
Roger wasn't murdered.
他是自杀的
He committed suicide.
法医给出了结果
The coroner's office made that determination
FBI也已证实
and the FBI confirmed it.
他们调查不够深入
They didn't look hard enough.
伊桑  我了解我的儿子
Ethan, I know my son.
他没有自杀
He did not kill himself.
他没有压抑  没理由自杀
He wasn't depressed. He had no reason.
如果有理由呢
What if he did have a reason?
我岂会不知
I would have known.
你不知  因为他没告诉你
Not if he didn't tell you.
自愧而不敢告诉你
Not if he was too ashamed to tell you
以及总统
or the president.
你说什么
What are you talking about?
SCC本打算对罗杰进行内部交易的调查
Roger was about to be investigated by the sec for insider trading.
他利用了特殊的信息渠道
He'd used information he only could have gotten through
与总统的接近
his access to the president.
在SCC还未开展调查之前
Before the sec opened the investigation,
他自杀了
he killed himself.
我不信
I don't believe it.
都在这儿
It's all in here.
sec文件里都有记录
In the sec case file.
为什么我才听说此事
Why is this the first time I'm hearing about this?
弗兰克·博伊兰同意搁置此案
Frank boylan agreed to bury the case.
作为对总统的政治帮助
As a political favor to the president.
我妻子知道此事  因此不告诉我
My wife knew about this and she didn't tell me?
她想告诉你
She wanted to.
但她更想保护你对儿子的记忆
But she also wanted to protect your memory of your son.
你沉浸于痛苦之中
You were in so much pain.
该死  伊桑  他是我儿子  我有权知道
Damn it, Ethan. He was my son. I deserve the truth.
不该对你隐瞒
And keeping it from you was a terrible mistake.
我现在意识到了
I realize that now.
但总统和我都认为
But the president and I both thought you were
你已经重新步入生活了
moving on with your life.
卡宁先生
Mr. Kanin.
总统要见您
The president wants to see you.
她知道你告诉我此事吗
Does she know you're telling me this now?
不  我认为我们最好继续心照不宣
No. And I think it best we keep it that way,
至少等此次危机解决之后
at least till this crisis is resolved.
我认为必须告诉他  抱歉  先生
I feel I have to tell him, sir. I'm sorry.
好的  谢谢
Alright, thank you.
总统阁下  你要见我
Madam president, you wanted to see me?
史密斯上将给出了撤军时间表
Admiral Smith laid out the timeline of withdrawing our forces.
他说为满足杜巴库的要求
He's saying to meet Dubaku's demands,
我们必须在下午1点前发令撤离
we need to order the pullback by 1 pm.
时间紧迫
That's not much time.
是的
No, it isn't.
也许阿尔梅达会告诉我们CIP装置在哪
Well maybe this Almeida will tell us where to find the CIP device.
不  提姆·伍兹刚从调查局收到消息
No. Tim Woods just heard from the Bureau.
目前为止  阿尔梅达拒绝合作
So far Almeida's refusing to cooperate.
也许他是在故作姿态  想要开条件
Well maybe he's just positioning for a deal.
提姆认为不是
Tim doesn't think so.
他说我们不能指望阿尔梅达开口
He said we shouldn't count on Almeida to talk.
明白了
I see.
所以
So
除非我命令军队撤退
unless I order our forces to stand down.
否则我将给美国人民带来死亡
I'll be condemning innocent Americans to death.
但如果我方屈服
And if we capitulate,
无数桑加拉人民将遭屠杀
thousands of Sangalas will be slaughtered.
怎么会这样  ethan
How did this happen, Ethan?
我们竟如此麻痹大意
How could we been so caught off guard,
逼我在两难之中做出抉择
and now I have to decide between two impossible choices.
至少其中一者尚有机会
Well, at least one of those choices does stand a good chance
保住美国人民的生命
of preserving American lives.
你是说撤退
You mean withdrawal.
时间不多  我们必须考虑此可能性
We are nearing the time and we have to consider it.
还没到这境地  ethan
We're not there yet, Ethan.
我不能讨论此事
I can't discuss this.
先要尝试所有可能的其他选择
Not until we have explored every possible option.
让FBI继续审问阿尔梅达
Tell the FBI to keep working on Almeida.
是  总统阁下
Yes, madam president.
布坎南  安全线路设置完成
Mr. Buchanan. I've got the secure line.
好的  接通他
All right. Dial the number.
比尔  别打马虎眼了  究竟发生了什么
Bill, stop screwing around. Tell me what the hell is going on!
托尼不是恐怖份子  杰克
Jack, Tony is not a terrorist.
他正执行卧底行动  同我合作
He's working deep cover. He's working with me.
有证据表明他曾试图摧毁两架商务客机
We have proof that he tried to bring down two commercial airliners.
你不明白他的处境
You don't know the whole story.
这是行动的一部分
That's part of an ongoing operation.
行动  什么行动
Operation? What kind of operation
会危机到成百上千的生命
puts hundreds if not thousands of lives in danger.
杰克
Jack, please.
听我说
You need to listen.
政府腐败不堪
Our government is corrupted.
政府内部有人
There are people on the inside
积极帮助dubaku和朱玛篡权
who are actively aiding Dubaku and Juma regime.
问题是  托尼本该守在CIP模块边
Point is Tony was supposed to be near the CIP module the whole time.
他被捕后  我们便无法
With him in custody, we've lost our ability
控制并破坏此阴谋
to control it and to attack this conspiracy.
谁参与了此阴谋  给我名字
Who's a part of the conspiracy? Give me names.
我们不知道具体人员
We don't know the extent of it.
我们有理由相信
We have reason to believe
总统的内阁成员牵涉其中
that members of the president's inner council are on payroll.
谁向你透露的消息  哪个机构
Who's sheperding you this information? Which agency?
别追问了  杰克  没有人透露消息
Let's just take it, Jack. There's no sheperd.
也没有机构  此次腐败牵涉甚广
There is no agency. This corruption runs deep and wide.
我们是背着政府在行动
We're working outside the government.
因此必须让托尼恢复卧底身份
It's why we have to get Tony back under cover.
他可是在FBI总部  比尔
He's at FBI headquarters, Bill.
我知道此事不易
I never said it's gonna be easy.
但我们必须尽力而为
But we have to try.
克罗伊已进入他们的系统
Chloe is already into their system.
克罗伊也参与此事
Chloe's working on this?
杰克  听到你的声音真好
Hi, Jack. It's good to hear your voice.
你也是
Yeah. You, too.
我在公共事务频道看到了你的听证会
I saw the hearing on c span
不敢相信参议员竟如此对你
I can't believe what the senator said to you.
你看上去很沉着
You looked good go.
杰克  我们需要你帮忙把托尼弄出来
Jack we need your help to get Tony out of there.
有位FBI探员蕾妮·沃克  她可以帮忙
There's an agent at the FBI Renee Walker. She could help.
不行  FBI有内鬼
No, the FBI has been compromised.
调查局内部有人暗中帮助杜巴库
Somebody in the bereau is aiding Dubaku.
你不明白  比尔  杰克  我信任她
You don't understand, Bill, jack, I trust her.
如果你认为必须用到她
Jack, if you think you need to use her
才能把托尼弄出FBI总部  那就听你的
to get Tony out of FBI headquarters, then do it.
但你此举会让她成为众矢之的
But you'll be making her a target.
你说得对
No, you're right.
你说得对  按你说的  我可以独自找到托尼
You're right. We'll do it your way. I can get to Tony myself.
但克罗伊得想法把我们弄出去
But Chloe's gonna have to get us outside the building.
我们已开始行动
We're already on it.
准备好了通知我
Get back to me as soon as you are ready.
我上路了  克罗伊
I'm on my way, Chloe.
西恩  我们上周下载的数据挖掘插件
Hey, Sean. You know these data mining plugins we downloaded last week,
存放在哪里了
where do we file those?
Where do we file those?
A76文件夹
Yeah. File folder A76.
你需要帮忙吗
Do you need help with something?
不用  怎么
No. Why?
你看上去很困惑
You seem confused.
我只是不喜欢在4级防范禁闭中工作
I just don't like having to dance around this level-4 lockdown.
我还以为你想找机会抱怨一番
Oh, well, I thought you welcomed the opportunity to complain about something.
喂
Hello?
泰勒先生  我是萨曼莎
Mr. Taylor. It's Samantha.
我本打算找你的
I was going to call you.
我要向你道歉  萨姆
I owe you an apology, Sam.
我不该那样质疑你
I was wrong to confront you like that.
不  你没错
Uh, no. You weren't.
我并未对你完全坦诚
I wasn't completely honest to you.
什么意思
What do you mean?
罗杰没有自杀  taylor先生
Roger didn't commit suicide, Mr. Taylor.
他是被谋杀的
He was murdered.
我想单独见你
I need to see you. Alone.
你能来吗
Will you meet me?
当然
Of course.
CIP装置在哪  托尼
Where is the CIP device, Tony?
你给谁了
Who would you gave it to?
付给你的这些家伙
People you're taking money from.
你也许想看看他们的杰作
Thought you might like to see some of their handywork.
你知不知道自从他们回到桑加拉
You know how many people they've killed
他们已屠杀了多少人
since they went back into Sangala?
20万人  还在不断上升
Two hundred thousand and counting.
绝大多数是女人和孩子
Most of them women and children.
托尼
Tony.
难道你的良心希望如此吗
You really want this on your conscience?
我问心无愧
My conscience is clear.
你说什么做什么都没用
There's nothing you can say or do will change that.
你还是放聪明些
So why don't you do the smart thing
劝泰勒总统撤走她的打击力量
and tell president Taylor to stand down the strike force?
如若不从
Because unless she does,
就等着天上下飞机雨吧
planes will be falling from the sky.
到时候你就有一整本新的照片可以观赏
And then you'll have a whole new batch of photoes to look at.
但这次  死的将是美国人
Only this time, they'll be of dead Americans.
拉里  我们谈谈
Larry, we need to talk.
阿尔梅达不会屈服的
Almeida's not gonna break.
未必
We don't know that.
他是训练有素的CTU探员
He's a trained CTU agent.
他作为审讯者经历过同样的审讯
He's conducted interrogations just like this one.
你能说的任何话
There's nothing you can say to him
他都早已对自己说过千遍
that he hasn't said to himself a hundred times.
那你有何建议  放弃
So what are you suggesting? We give up?
不是  我建议采取更强硬的方式
No. I'm suggesting we might need more forceful approach.
你指刑讯
You mean torture.
有多种高压审讯方式
No, there are methods of coercion
我们尚未考虑
that we haven't even considered. Pharmaceuticals...
不敢相信你会这么说
I can't believe you wanna have this conversation.
我还没有提出论点
You're not hearing the argument...
你的论点疯狂至极  这是违法的
The argument is crazy. It's illegal.
不许再提  说真的  我要鲍尔离开
And it's over. As a matter of fact, I want Bauer out of here.
他是不稳定因素  留下他太危险了
He's a wildcard. He's dangerous.
我要他马上离开大楼
I want him out of the building.
去给他办手续  我继续审问
Go. Process him out. I will continue here.
快走
Go. Go! Now.
蕾妮  我正要给你打电话
Renee, I was just about to call you.
我可能发现内鬼了
I may have found the leak.
有人在4极防范禁闭下露出了马脚
Someone did a runaround under level-4 lockdown.
他们绕过了安全防火墙
They circumvented the security fence
并侵入了航空局的数据库
and they hacked into the FAA database.
航空局  你确定
FAA, are you sure?
确定  我不清楚他们在做什么
Positive. I don't what they were doing in there,
但必须使用极复杂的外挂软件才能实现
but they had to navigate some very sophisticated tagger software.
几分钟前
Just a few minutes ago.
知道是谁吗
Any idea who it was?
不知  但我可以查出登陆终端的账号
No. But I may be able to pull out user ID out of the terminal.
好的  哪个终端
Okay, which terminal?
主机房  三号终端
Main frame room, terminal three.
-赶快查  有消息告诉我  -好的
- Check it out. Let me know what you find. - Ok.
泰勒探员
Agent Tyler.
你把杰克·鲍尔的简报资料准备好
I need you to prepare the briefing package for Jack Bauer
把他的个人物品给我
and bring me his personal effects.
好的  马上拿来
Yeah, I'll bring them right to you.
谢谢  我就在办公室
Thanks. I'll be in my office.
上次登陆  西恩·希林格
Last login: Sean Hillinger
你在干什么
What are you doing?
怎么回事
What's the matter?
你在原地别动
Just, you just stay where you're.
詹尼斯  住手
Janis, stop it.
你说句话好吗
Would you just talk to me?
我知道你在帮助托尼·阿尔梅达
I know you've been helping Tony Almeida.
什么  你疯了不成
What? Are you crazy?
没有
No.
你侵入了航管局数据库
You broke into the FAA database,
那是你的服务器名称
that's your server ID.
对  是我的服务器ID
Yes, my server ID,
可我没有协助恐怖分子
but I'm not helping the terrorists,
你想知道我为何去那里
you wanna know why I was in there,
告诉你  因为我担心
I'll tell you, I was worried.
我妻子在其中一架飞机上
My wife on of those planes up there,
我想知道她的飞机是否已被禁飞
I had to see if her flight had been grounded yet.
你以为我会信这鬼话吗
You expect me to believe that?
你为何鬼鬼祟祟
Why are you sneeking around?
四级锁定模式把我踢出了航管局数据库
'cause the level 4 lockdown cut me out of the FAA database
我没法了解她的航班动向
I couldn't monitor her flight.
你自己来看
Look, see for yourself.
从赌城起飞的112号航班
Flight 112 out of the Las Vegas.
克里斯蒂娜·希林格
Christina Hillinger
好  待在那里别动
Okay, just stay there.
克里斯蒂娜·希林格
CHRISTINA HILLINGER
天啊  肖恩  你吓死我了
God, Shawn, you scared the hell outta me,
为何不早说
why wouldn't you just tell me that?
因为那是在打擦边球
'cause what I was doing was borderline illegal,
不想让你惹上麻烦
I didn't wanna get you in trouble.
你当时也焦头烂额了
plus, you looked like you've had enough on your plate.
可恶  我刚上报说有安全漏洞
Damn it, I told Renee I'd found a security leak.
出了什么事
Is that what's going on around here?
只是安全漏洞吗
There's just a security leak?
别管了  回到你的工作台
Don't worry about it, go back to your station,
不要声张
keep this to yourself
我会为你收拾这烂摊子
and I will clean up your mess.
去吧
Go.
白痴
Idiot.
请讲
Go ahead.
杰克  沃克探员在走廊里
Jack, agent Walker is on her way,
她正向你房间这边走来
she's heading down the corridor toward your room.
收到
Copy that.
你的循环程序进展如何
How are you doing with the loops?
正在投掷第一个循环
I'm dropping the first one in now.
我有一系列循环程序
I have a series of loops
你边走我边投
and I'm dropping them as you go.
保安不会发现
Security won't see a thing.
明白
Understand.
原地待命
Standing by.
抱歉  杰克  我们的行动没带上你
Sorry, Jack. We're proceeding without you.
不是我的决定
Wasn't my decision.
没有你  我们抓不到阿尔梅达
Well, we would't have Almeida without you,
我们欠你人情
we own you alot.
谢了
Thanks.
是要我签字的文件吗
That paperwork for me?
嗯  要你填一下
Yeah, you need to fill this out.
我会在司法部为你美言几句
I'm gonna put in a good word with the Justice Department for you.
也许会有帮助
Maybe it will help.
谢了
Thanks.
杰克
Jack.
别挣扎
Don't fight it.
杰克
Jack.
别挣扎
Don't fight it.
杰克勒晕了沃克探员
Jack just took out agent Walker,
拿到了她的密匙和武器
he has her keycard and her weapon.
他正去救托尼
He's going to get Tony.
你在什么位置
What's your location.
大约十分钟后到达
About ten minutes out.
收到我发的会合地点了吗
Did you get my rendezvous point?
刚在GPS上显示出来
Just showed up on my GPS.
很好
Okay, great...
我先挂线  杰克打电话来了
I gotta go, it's Jack.
杰克
Jack?
准备完毕  我可以进入一号审讯室了
I'm ready.I've got access to Interrogation One,
比尔何时到
what's Bill's ETA?
大约十分钟
About ten minutes.
走廊里什么情况
How's the corridor?
安全
Clear.
等我答复
Wait for my call.
放下武器  快
Put your weapons down, now!
你这是干什么
What the hell do you think you're doing?
我让你立即放下武器
I said do it now!
不然我杀了他
Do it or I will kill him.
好  好吧
Okay, all right.
放下  没事  放下吧
Put it down, it's all right, do it.
慢点  慢点
Slowly, slowly.
该你了  快点
Now, you. Do it!
好吧
All right.
把枪踢给我
Kick the weapon over to me.
快
Come on.
好  好
Okay, all right.
给他解开手铐
Uncuff him.
沃克探员人在哪里
Where's agent Walker?
你把她怎样了
What did you do to her?
闭嘴
Shut up!
鲍尔  你没法得逞的
Bauer, you're gonna make it outta here.
我让你闭嘴
I said shut up.
我和比尔通过话了
I talked to Bill.
他告诉过你多少事
How much did he tell you?
够多了  我们要把你救出去
Enough, we're gonna get you outta here.
克罗伊已经侵入了保安系统
Chole's tapped into the security.
她会指引我们出去
She's gonna walk us outta this building,
你跟着我就行
all you need to do is follow my lead.
克罗依  我是杰克  收到了吗
Chole, it's Jack, do you copy?
收到  杰克
Copy, Jack.
我和托尼在通向走廊的一号审讯室门口
I got Tony at the door of Interrogation One leading out to the hallway.
好  看到了
Okay, I see you,
我带你们去西南出口
I'm gonna direct you to the southwest exit.
你们当前在这栋建筑人口最稀少的区域
Right now you're in the least populated area of the building.
不过在你们出去前会遇到很多险阻
But you're gonna run into a lot more resistance before you get outta there.
收到  准备好了吗
Copy that, you ready?
可以行动了
Clear to move.
走
Let's go.
等下  有两个人要下电梯
Hold on, there're two people coming out of the elevator.
收到  来吧
Copy that, come on.
杰克  我为我先前说过的话道歉
Listen, Jack, i'm sorry for the stuff I said back there.
为了告诉你比尔的代号
Just needed to get you close enough
必须让你接近我
to give you Bill's codename.
我没拧断你的脖子真是万幸
Just glad I didn't break you neck.
差一点
Well, you came close.
嗯  不好意思
Yeah, sorry about that.
好了  安全
Okay, clear.
安全了
We're clear.
清理完了你的蛛丝马迹
I cleaned up your trail,
这次违规不要对第三人说
we will just keep this transgression between us.
尽管我还不知道该怎么对蕾妮说
Although I don't know what I'm gonna tell Renee.
你听到我说什么了吗
Have you heard one thing I've just said?
嗯  好  看看这个
Yeah, yeah, that's fine, take a look at this.
什么
What?
一个信号路由器性能出现异常
There's a performance hit on one of our signal routers,
下降了0.7%
It's down 0.7%
你说的对  有人在侵占我们的带宽
You're right, somebody is riding our bandwith.
侵入系统  可能吗  有那么多防火墙
Hecking in, is that possible? With all the safeguards?
如果是行家
Anything is possible
一切都有可能
if you know what you're doing.
他们在我们的安全子网里
They're inside our security sub-net.
已经侵入了监视系统
They've accessed the surveillance system.
你想怎么办
What are you gonna do?
锁定他们
Lock them out.
杰克  沿着下个走廊左转
Okay, Jack, you're gonna make a left down the next hallway.
路尽头有个消防梯
There's an emergency stairwell at the end.
消防梯通向地面吗
Will that stairwell get us down the ground level?
对
Yes.
收到
Copy that.
等下
Hold on.
什么事
What's wrong?
失去传输信号了
I lost my feed.
克罗依那里的信号出现故障
Chole's feed just went down.
你做了什么
What did you do?
我测试了那条线路  让它重启了
I've pinged the line and it automatically reset.
确实有人侵入
Someone was hacking in,
屏蔽了我们的监视摄像机
they were taking out our surveillance cameras.
詹尼斯  看这个
Janis, take a look at this.
发给我
Send it to me.
保安  我是詹尼斯·古德
Security, this is Janis Gold.
出现代号12情况
We have a code 12 in progress,
派人去一号审讯室
we need a team to Interrogation One.
是  女士  立即派人
Yes, ma'am, right away.
所有探员  出现安全漏洞  代号12
All agents, security breach, code 12.
我们得继续走  走吧
We gotta keep moving, let's go.
保安人员在我们和西南出口之间
Security team between us at the southwest exit.
克罗依  你怎么样  我们被困
Chloe, what have you got? We're boxed in.
联调局的人在拦截我
Someone at FBI is blocking my every move,
气死我了
it's really starting to piss me off.
重新进入他们系统
You need to get them back into their system,
否则我们无法脱身
otherwise we're not gonna make it outta here.
杰克  对不起  我在努力
Jack, I'm sorry, I'm trying.
我得走了  杰克
We've got make a move, Jack.
我知道
I know.
走吧
Let's go now.
克罗依  说话
Chole, talk to me.
我还是被锁定  在想办法
I'm still locked out, trying to work around it.
杰克  留在这里  我们坐以待毙
Jack, we're sitting ducks if we stay here.
我知道
I know.
克罗依  我们别无选择
Chole, we have to take the stairwell,
必须走楼梯
we don't have a choice.
悄悄地
Quietly.
他们在哪里
Where are they?
在查
We're looking.
找到他们
Find them.
你没事吧
Are you all right?
嗯  没事  你还好吧
Yeah, yeah, I'm fine, are you okay?
嗯
Yeah.
他们还在楼内  我们在找他们
They're still in the buidling, we're trying to locate them.
真没想到  杰克这是在干什么
I can't believe this, what the hell is Jack doing?
他是在帮他朋友逃跑
He's helping his friend escape, that's what he's doing.
拉里  对不起  我不该相信他
I'm--I'm sorry, Larry. I shouldn't have trusted him.
找到他们了
I got them.
西南角楼梯
Southwest stairwell.
保安  我是莫斯
Security, this is Moss,
嫌犯正从西南角楼梯下楼
suspects are from southwest stairwell, descending.
刚下到五楼
Pass the fifth floor.
封锁大楼周边
Lock on the building perimeter
派两队人去一楼专用通道
and deploy two teams in the first floor service corridor.
注意  嫌犯持有武器
Be aware, the suspects are armed.
活捉他们
We need them alive.
我重新登陆了  杰克
Okay, I'm back up, Jack.
收到
Copy that.
怎么回事
What was that?
黑客又回来了
Heckers' back in,
不管是谁  这些人都是非常厉害
whoever this is, they're very good.
锁定他们
Well, lock them out.
在努力
I'm trying.
怎么了
What is it?
前面有埋伏  六人小队
You're heading into an ambush, the six-man team.
他们正从楼梯向上走
They're heading up toward you in the stairwell.
他们从楼梯来了
They're coming on the stairs.
给我灭火器
Pass me that fire extinguisher.
我们在停车场屋顶
We're on the roof of the parking lot.
看到你们了  干得好
I see you, good work.
去北端  杰克
Go to the north end, Jack.
比尔快到了
Bill's almost there.
他驾驶的是蓝色货车
He's in the blue van.
收到
Copy that.
他们在外面  从三楼窗户出去的
They're outside, they went through the third floor window.
封锁小队  他们在停车场
Perimeter team, they're in the parking garage.
通知片警  让他们封锁五条街内的区域
Notify Matro police, have them corden off a five-block perimeter.
小心右边  蹲下
On the right, get down.
必须让你回去继续做卧底
We gotta get you outta here and back undercover,
我随后就到  快走
I will be right behind you, go.
这个滋味不会好受
This is gonna hurt.
托尼  走啊
Tony, let's go.
来  杰克
Come on, Jack.
开车  比尔
Go, Bill.
莫斯探员  他们跑了
Agent Moss, they're gone,
跑出了包围圈
they got outside the perimeter.
克罗依  我接到他们了
All right, Chole, I got them,
他们追来了吗
any sign of pursuit?
还没有  一定在调动人手
Not so far, they must be still mobilizing,
我们奇袭成功
we caught them off guard.
交通监视器
Traffice cams.
我在循环频率来扫清障碍
I'm cycling the frequcies to clear path now.
好
Good.
没事吧
Are you all right?
没事  我们要去哪里
I'm fine, where are we going?
不远处
It's not far.
比尔  我按你说的救出了托尼
Bill, I did what you wanted, I got Tony out of there.
告诉我怎么回事
Tell me what's going on?
到达目的地后  我全告诉你
When we get there, I will tell you everything.